Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Issues, 1930-2004; 1; 58.4 cubic ft.
  - Water, 1930-1995; 1.15; 7.0 cubic ft.
    - Great Lakes, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Great Lakes, "A Citizen's Guide to the Great Lakes Water Quality Agreement", 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Great Lakes Fish and Wildlife Restoration Act of 1990, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), 6/1-2/1995, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Agenda, Work, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Background, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Buffalo, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Conference Notes, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Focus Groups, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Lake Ontario Health and Environment Directory, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Mailing List, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Michigan State University, Invitations, 1993; 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), New York State Division of Water Technical and Operational Guidance, 1985-1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Antidegradation, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Coastal and Ocean Resources Conference, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Site Information, 1992-1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), Steering Committee, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), University of Rochester Conference, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), University of Rochester Conference, Replies and Requests, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Great Lakes Initiative (GLI), University of Rochester Workshop, Invitation, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Great Lakes Toxins, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Groundwater, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Groundwater, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Groundwater, Booth Report, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Groundwater, Department of Environmental Conservation, New York, 1981-1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Groundwater, Department of Environmental Conservation, New York, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Groundwater, Federal, 1980-1982; 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Groundwater, General Information, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Groundwater, Legislation, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Groundwater, News Clippings, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Groundwater, Pesticides, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Hudson River, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Hudson River, Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Hudson River, PCB, 1983; 1988-1996 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Hudson River, Reports, 1979; 1983; 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Hudson River, Reports, 1985; 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Hudson River, Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Hudson River, Reports, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - A Guide to New York City's Reservoirs, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Hearing on Organic Chemicals in Drinking Water, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Inventory, Community Water Systems: New York State Volume I Municipal, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Hudson, River, Reports, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Hudson River, Reports, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Hudson River, Toxins, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Hudson River, Westway, 1976; 1984 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Hudson River, Westway, 1988; 1994 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Lakes, Aquatic Weed Control, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Lakes, Black Flies, Mosquitoes, and Gypsy Moths, 1981; 1984; 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Lakes, Daminozide (Alar), 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Lakes, General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Lakes, Great Lakes, 1979-1984 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Lakes, Great Lakes, 1985-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Lakes, Great Sacandaga Lake, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Lakes, Lake Champlain, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Lakes, Lake Champlain Plan, 1995 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Lakes, Lake George, 1978-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Lakes, Lake George, 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Legislation, 1985-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Long Island, Status of State Safe Drinking Water System, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Long Island Sound, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Long Island Sound Study (LISS), 1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Long Island Sound Study (LISS), 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Long Island Sound Study (LISS), 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Long Island Sound Watershed Directory, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Nassau Forum, 1992-1996 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - New York City, Natural Resources Defense Council, 1994 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - New York State, 25 Year Plan for the Great Lakes, 1992 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Nonpoint Source Assessment Report, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Nonpoint Source Pollution Management Program, Department of Conservation, 1986-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Nonpoint Source Pollution Management Program, Department of Conservation, 1989-1992 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Nonpoint Source Contamination of Groundwater, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Ocean Dumping, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Oil Spills, 1990-1991; 1993 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Onondaga Lake, 1984; 1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Prattsville Pump Station, 1981-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Prattsville Pump Storage, 1970-1979 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Proposition 65, California, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Proposition 65, California, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Proposition 65, California, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Proposition 65, California, News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Proposition 65, California, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Regional Forums, 1995 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Reservoir Release Regulations, 1977; 1980; 1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Rivers, Hudson, 1979-1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Rivers, Hudson, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Rivers, St. Lawrence, 1984; 1993 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Rivers, Wild, Scenic, and Recreational River Systems, 1930; 1975-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Rivers, Wild, Scenic, and Recreational River Systems, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Rivers, Wild, Scenic, and Recreational River Systems, Legislation, 1975-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Sewage Sludge, 1977; 1981-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Sewage Treatment Funding Proposal, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - State Safe Driving Water Act, Activist Network, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, General Information, 1986-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, General Information, 1987-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, New York State Assembly Person Addresses, 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, Other States, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, Proposition 65, 1967; 1986-1991 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, Water Quality Standards, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - State Safe Drinking Water Act, Working Files, 1986-1990 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Technical Information, 1986-1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Testimony of Landon Marsh, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Tug Hill, General Information, 1976-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Waste Water Treatment, 1971; 1981-1982 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Waste Water Treatment, 1983-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Water, 208 Bulletin, 1975-1980 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Water Bulletin, 1980-1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Water Conservation, 1985-1989 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Water Development, 1977 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Water Finance Authority, 1981-1983 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Water Laws (not CWA), 1974; 1980-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Water Management Advisory Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Water Management Advisory Committee, 1991-1994 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Water Management Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Water Management Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Water Metering, 1981-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Water Pollution, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Water Quality, 1968; 1979-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Water Quality, 1983-1992 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Water Quality, 1985-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Water Quality, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Water Quality, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Water Quality, Publications, 1979-1985 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Water Quality Regulation, Department of Environmental Conservation, Reports, 1984 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Water Quality Regulation, Department of Environmental Conservation, Reports, 1985-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Water Quality Regulation, Department of Environmental Conservation, Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Water Quality, Standards, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Water Supply, 1979-1982 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Water Supply, 1983-1986 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Water Supply, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Zero Discharge, Toxic Substances, Waste Reduction, 1986-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Between the Railroad and the River, 1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Clean Water/Jobs Coalition, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Five Rivers Master Plan, 1993 Update (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Follensby Pond: An Unbelievable Acquisition Opportunity, Undated (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - New York/New Jersey/Harbor Estuary Program, Undated (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Proposed Surface Water Filtration and Disinfection Requirements, 1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Rapp, O., "Watching Big Brother"Times Union, 1990 December 09 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Toxic Contamination in Large Lakes, 1978-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Watertest Corporation, Undated (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Great Lakes Initiative, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Great Lakes Initiative, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
  - Wetlands, 1975-1995; 1.16; 1.4 cubic ft.
    The subseries Wetlands contains material related to coastal erosion and coastal zone management in New York.
    - Coastal Erosion, New York State, 1980-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Coastal Erosion, New York State, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Coastal Erosion, New York State, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Coastal Resources, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Coastal Resources, Legislation, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Coastal Resources, Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Coastal Resources, Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Coastal Zone Management, Coastal Coalition Lists, 1980-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Coastal Zone Management, Federal, 1975-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Coastal Zone Management, New York Coastal Management Program, 1979-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Coastal Zone Management, New York Coastal Management Program, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Coastal Zone Management, New York Coastal Management Program, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Coastal Zone Management, New York Coastal Management Program, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Coastal Zone Management, New York Waterfront Revitalization and Coastal Resources Act, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Coastal Zone Management, Newsletters, 1980-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Freshwater Wetlands, 1976-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Freshwater Wetlands, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - National Wildlife Federation and Clean Water Act, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - "News From...Hudsonia", 1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Regulations, 1976-1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Regulations, 1984-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Striped Bass, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Tidal Wetlands, 1972-1979 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Tidal Wetlands, 1981-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - The Young Scientists Introduction to Wetlands, Undated (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Washington Update, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
  - Wildlife, 1976-1991; 1.17; 2.0 cubic ft.
    The Wildlife subseries includes material related to birds, funding, bear-dog hunting, coyotes, and wildlife management in New York.
    - Animal Rights, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Avian Briefing Book, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Bear Dog Hunting, 1981; 1991; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Birds, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Botany, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Coyotes, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Endangered Species, 1987-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Essential Habitat, 1986; 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Essential Habitat Bill, 1983-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Essential Habitat Bills and Letters, 1979; 1985-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Funding, Annual Reports, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Funding, Coyotes, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Funding, Fish and Wildlife, News Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Funding, Great Lakes, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Funding, Hudson River, 1980-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Funding, Karner Blue Butterfly, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Funding, Lamprey, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Funding, Onondaga Lake, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - General Information, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - General Information and Background, 1981-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Habitat, Coastal Zone Management, 1982-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Habitat, Eagles and Raptors, 1986; 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Habitat, Legislation and Definitions, Memorandums, 1973; 1983-1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Habitat, Mud Turtle, Long Island Land Use, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Habitat, Physical Location of Habitat, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Habitat, Salamanders, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Habitat, "The Wilton Mall and the Loss of the Karner Blue: What can be Learned", Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Hudson River Habitat, 1989 Bill, 1988; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Legislation Material, 1977; 1980-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Legislation Material, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Legislative History, Essential Habitat Bill, 1979-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - List of Endangered Species, 1976; 1979; 1981-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Long Island Colonial Waterbird and Piping Plover Study, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - National Wildlife Federation, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Reports, 1978; 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Return a Gift to Wildlife, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Return a Gift to Wildlife, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Striped Bass, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Ward Stone, 1975; 1988-1990 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Wildlife Management, 1973-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Wildlife Management, Testimony, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Wildlife Pathology Unit, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Wildlife Reports, 1979; 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Wildlife Reports, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Wildlife Reports, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Wildlife Reports, 1988; 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
- Val Washington, 1985-1998; 2; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Val Washington served as executive director of Environmental Advocates from 1996-2004. The Val Washington series is further divided into two subseries: Hudson River Park and Subject Files.
  - Hudson River Park, 1996-1998; 2.1; 1.0 cubic ft.
    The subseries Hudson River Park contains correspondence, legislation and reports from the Hudson River Park Alliance Steering Committee, of which Washington was a member. Also included is the Environmental Impact Report of the proposed Hudson River Park.
    - Alliance Steering Committee, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 1)
    - Alliance Steering Committee, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 2)
    - Analysis of Financial Plan, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 3)
    - Concept and Financial Plan, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 6)
    - Environmental Impact Statement, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 7)
    - Environmental Impact Statement, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 8)
    - Environmental Impact Statement, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Impact Statement, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and Agenda, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 11)
    - Land Trust Alliance Seminar, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 13)
    - News Clippings, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 14)
    - New York State Legislation, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 15)
  - Subject Files, 1985-1998; 2.2; 1.0 cubic ft.
    The Subject Files subseries contains material of an administrative nature generated by Washington during her tenure as executive director of Environmental Advocates.
    - Adirondack Solid Waste Agreement, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 1)
    - Akzo Nobel Salt, Inc., Case, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 2)
    - Alternative Fuels Air Guide, Undated (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Warren M., Legislative Breakfast, 1996; 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 4)
    - Blue Mountain Lake Board and Staff Retreat, 1989 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 5)
    - Bond Act, Coalition and Steering Committee, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 6)
    - Bond Act, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 7)
    - Bond Act, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 8)
    - Bond Act, Drafting and Funding, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 9)
    - Bond Act, Implementation, Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 10)
    - Children with Lead Poisoning, Survey, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 11)
    - City of Newburg, Contamination, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 12)
    - Committee on Director, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 14)
    - Energy Foundation, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 15)
    - Enlibra: A New Shared Doctrine for Environment Management, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 16)
    - Essex County, Landfill, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 17)
    - Great Lakes, Water Diversion, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 18)
    - Healthy Cities, Healthy Kids, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 19)
    - Healthy Schools Network, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 20)
    - Hudson River Valley, Greenway Act, Revisions, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Val Washington), Folder 21)